This is
an
awesome treasure
hidden at the end of the sea,
and anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the compass points our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
What?
They ran away and left the island?
Yes, we couldn't even give them a gift.
How disappointing.
And after all they did for us, I wonder if
they realize how much we appreciate them.
I agree.
They don't know how we feel.
You know, Issie,
it's not fair that you were the only
one that got to say goodbye to them.
Everyone's really upset that we
let our heroes just run away.
Sorry, Luffy and the others made
me promise to keep it a secret.
Hey, Lock, did you see?
Luffy can stretch his body really far.
He's like a Gum-Gum pistol. Cape! Yay!
Issie, please, you've got to hold still.
I never knew there were warriors
like him in the Blue Sea.
I want to be just like him when I grow up.
A Gum-Gum warrior.
Issie.
I'm just going to trim your hair a little.
You need to let it grow.
Hey, it'll look good.
I think you've forgotten you're a girl.
And girls should look cute.
What? Cute? Me?
Are you nuts?
I'm not With the war over,
there's no need for kids like
you to carry weapons anymore.
Now you can enjoy life the way it was
meant to be, and as a proper young lady.
I never knew you were so ladylike.
Come on, Issie. Now hold still.
Lucky's ladylike!
Issie!
Great warrior Call 'gara, we were told
the Shandorian's role has been fulfilled.
As for your last wish, it was
delivered to your best friend.
Our future generations will
no longer have to shed blood.
We are finally at peace.
The war may be over, but one thing
that will never end is our pride.
Please continue to guide us, mighty
Kalgara, and watch over us as well.
We solemnly swear, the fire
of Shandora will never die.
I cannot abandon my duties.
I am the Sky Knight, after all.
Perhaps you should be looking at yourself.
Remember, this city originally
belonged to your people.
It did, long ago.
But that means nothing now.
In fact, with this battle,
all of us realized something.
Birth belongs to no group.
It must be shared.
Our world has two sides.
The land is called
Skypiea, the city Shandora.
They have been torn
asunder by war for ages.
Only a man who has long lamented that
war can unite them and that man is you.
So, Sky Knight Gonfall, I'd like
you to take Skypiea's throne again.
Only you can heal the deep wounds
that scar this land of ours.
We'd like you to do it too, sir.
Gonfall, please!
We Shandians are behind you all the way.
Yeah!
Gonfall, yeah!
Please come back!
Well, well.
And here I was thinking
that I'd finally be able
to get some rest and
tend to my pumpkin patch.
Okay we're almost there everyone see that
up ahead that's cloud end whoa let me see
huh so that's where we go back down
from we got here sooner than i thought
oh we really have to go back already you
know it sounds crazy but i'm actually
gonna miss this place I think it's
time we said goodbye to the White Sea.
Sky Island Sheer is fun, but scary, too.
We just go through that
gate and there'll be
a milky road that'll
take us to the Blue Sea,
huh?
Wonder if we'll ever
visit this place again.
Well, you never know.
I'm sorry, but this is
as far as we can go.
Goodbye, my friends!
Take care of yourselves!
We will!
Thanks for the escort! Conis!
Don't forget me, Angel!
Say goodbye to the others for us!
See ya!
It was nice meeting you guys.
Thanks for everything.
No!
You've got it wrong!
We're the ones who should be thanking you!
We'll never forget you!
Thanks to you all!
Goodbye, Conis, old guy
furball! Take care now! Bye!
Now take in your sails and hold on tight.
You're in for a bumpy ride. Right.
Let's do as the man says.
It feels like we're
already picking up speed.
Yeah, we're sliding down from
thousands of feet in the air.
Hurry up! Huh?
What the?
He says don't leave without me.
Oh, that's the south bird
we brought up here with us.
Captain, it looks like the log post has
the coordinates for the next island.
Great, let's go!
Once we get to the bottom, we're
going to start a brand new adventure.
Close up for finding some gold.
Guys, get ready!
Blue Sea, here we come!
Everyone, grab hold of something!
The freefall's about to start!
Freefall?
Pass!
Just hang on.
One octopus balloon, on the way.
Octopus!
What the?
Well, that hurt.
What happened?
Hey, guys!
Get a load of this!
What the hell is it? A balloon!
Yeah, ain't it great?
We're not falling! Oh, good.
For a minute there, I
thought we were goners.
All of us.
keep ringing it let the
departing heroes of this
land know how much we
appreciate them Let's go!
Bluebeats!
Coming soon!
You're always welcome!
Thank you so much!
We let you say prizes to the Blue Sea!
When you look up, you see the sky.
Though some believe it
to be only a legend,
there is an island floating
thousands of feet in the air!
If you listen carefully, you
can hear the tolling of a bell!
It rings today and it will ring again!
Tomorrow that bell rings from the heavens!
From a land that wandered,
it sings of its pride and
proclaims to the rest of the world:
we are here!
This is so great!
Tell me about it!
What a way to travel!
I love it!
You're calling off the search? Of course.
The City of Gold has been
in the sky this whole time.
There's nothing else to be
found at the bottom of the sea.
Sorry, fellas.
This dream's over.
No point in staying here anymore.
Old man! Cricket!
I want to thank all of you for helping me
pursue my dream for all of these years.
You never stop believing.
That means a lot.
Does this mean...
You're leaving the Alliance?
Hey, guys.
Since this dream's done, which
one are we going to pursue next?
We'll all follow you to the ends
of the earth, old man! Yeah!
Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold!
We finally struck it rich!
What should we buy with all this loot?
Hey!
I know a huge bronze statue! Moron!
Only an idiot would
exchange gold for bronze!
How stupid!
What we need are more cannons!
Ten of them!
Ten!
Mommy!
I want to buy a refrigerator with a lock!
Aw, if you get one with a lock, there'll
be no way for me to get a midnight snack!
That's exactly why I want one, you pig!
Can you guys just hold on a second?
We need to land first, then
we can divide up the treasure!
Please buy me books!
If we buy everything you guys want,
we're gonna be broke again in no time!
The sun's completely set now.
It's still a nice view.
You're right.
It really is.
Cold!
Nami! Robin! Are you okay?
That was really scary.
What happened to the octopus?
Guess it ran out of air.
Wonder how that happened.
Come on!
Don't whine.
We did make it down here
alive. You're right.
And we got to see an incredible place.
Now that we're down here,
it looks so far away.
Like something out of a dream.
It's a dreamland.
Think we'll see it again?
Well, you might see someplace
similar when you die. Not you.
I doubt you're going
anyplace good. You jerk!
You guys keep discussing the afterlife.
Me, I'm gonna go put on a pot of coffee.
Make dinner instead, Sanji!
Are you ever not hungry?
Have some coffee first
and be patient, will ya?
Pirate treasure is always divided up.
Even after splitting up the loot,
we'd all have more gold than
we'd know what to do with.
Hey, wait!
I want to go and buy some stuff.
Like what?
Ooh, I tell you what I want to buy!
A big gold statue!
Oh, I want to buy a bunch
of new medical books.
New pots, frying pans,
silverware, giant mousetrap.
Wow, even after all that,
there'll still be a lot left over.
I could buy lots of booze.
But first, I take an extra cut. 80%.
Are you nuts?!
it's not for me oh yeah
then who and why should they
receive a bigger share than
the rest of us it's for a
special lady we're going to
set aside the gold to pay
for the repairs we need to
make lady oh wait you mean
the Mary that's right isn't
it about time we paid her
back for all she's done for
us well come to think of
it the going Mary has carried
us for a long time now
hasn't she ever since I joined
up and left my village in
the east blue and that's
exactly why we need to give
her some tender loving care
good idea the going Mary's
great repair let's do it
here dig in oh I've been
wondering how much longer
Usopp's half-ass repairs are
gonna last hey I'm a sniper
not a ship right right it's
time we took the Mary to a
real shipyard and got some
honest-to-goodness shipwrights
to give her the repairs
she needs so there are people
who can fix ships better
Yep,
sometimes when you need a job done right
you gotta go see a professional That's it!
We gotta get a shipwright for our crew!
Our journey's far from over, right?
We really need someone with those
skills And the Mary isn't just our ship,
she's our home too!
So let's go find us a shipwright
who can keep the Mary safe!
Well, I'm impressed.
Whoa, he got to the point!
That's pretty rare.
Well, that sounds really good to me.
Luffy, let's go do it!
That's what I just said.
I just hope we can find somebody good.
We should get a musician, too.
Let's forget that one.
What's all the ruckus out here?
Megway!
Quit pushing! Come on! Stop it!
Let me go! Why are they fighting?
Bellamy! Sargus!
Isn't someone gonna stop them?
No more!
I'm begging you!
Why are you making me do this?
What the hell is going on?
I've never seen Sargus bleed like that.
Why, you ask?
Why am I making you?
Sargus.
Bellamy.
I'm making you do this because
you've made a mockery of this symbol.
Does the Sky Island exist or not?
Is the legendary City of Gold real or not?
The truth doesn't really
matter now, does it?
You play the opposing sides off each
other to twist them to your will.
That's what I told you.
Right, Bellamy?
I think that's Don Quixote Don Flamingo.
He's one of the seven warlords of the sea!
I heard his bounty's over 300 million.
What's a guy like him doing here?
You've really let me down and I've got
zero tolerance for useless punks like you.
No, not again!
My body's moving on its own!
I can't control it! Please! No!
Bellamy!
Please
Just give me one more
chance to set things right!
I swear we'll loyally
follow your every command.
Bellamy Let it go, Bellamy!
I might have lost But I've never
once acted against your principles.
I swear on your symbol!
Please, I had reasons for my actions.
I couldn't just let the
Straw Hats get away.
They were bound to find you
someday if I didn't stop them.
What a touching sentiment.
Such genuine loyalty.
Your concern for my well-being
is duly noted, Bellamy.
There's a new era quickly approaching,
so your actions here won't really matter.
But I still have no use for you.
He wiped out Bellamy as
easily as stomping on a baby!
He was worth 55 million!
The beginning is upon us.
I suggest you prepare.
We're drawing close to a new world in
which only true pirates can survive.
The weak should run while they still can,
or be swept away by the
tides of time as they
roll back to reveal a
new era of champions!
As you climb into the night.
But your reflection wanes.
Then you disappear.
Fading so silently.
Stay as you are.
Don't lose your way.
Let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back.
Don't give up on your dreams.
They're windless nights.
They come to you.
All again and again.
Until you see the journey through.
You may not attend.
I hope that you'll learn.
To put your past behind.
And just keep moving on.